# MEGHAN MURPHY

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/meghan-murphy-111445179/

GitHub: https://github.com/MMURPHY222

Portfolio: COMING SOON

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavascriptES6+, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, React, MySQL, MongoDB, jQuery, Agile Methodologies, Express.js, Command Line, Git

## **PROJECTS**

Market Finder – Website allowed users to enter their zip code and be presented with a list of farmers markets within their area. Also, allowed for recipe searches based on ingredients. -- HTML, CSS, Javascript, APIs -- <a href="https://github.com/MMURPHY222/Project-1">https://github.com/MMURPHY222/Project-1</a>
https://mmurphy222.github.io/Project-1/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### 1/2021-5/2021 Teacher's Aide, The Paideia School - Atlanta, Georgia

• Facilitated activities that fostered learning, community, and understanding among kids age three to four years old

### 1/2021-Present Barista, Waller's Coffee Shop - Atlanta, Georgia

• While on shift covered transactions with customers, made drinks and food per order, prepared food for the next shift. Organized and communicated with bands coming for shows in evenings throughout setup.

# **EDUCATION**

# Aug 2017 -- Dec 2020

BS Anthropology and Human Biology, Atlanta, Emory University

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer

Georgia Tech Web Developer Bootcamp Certification 6/2021-9/2021

College varsity athlete who attended an academically rigorous university and balanced practice schedule with classes. Experienced communicator and team member willing to challenge myself day to day.